[
	{
		"question": "What color is the tongue of a giraffe?",
		"options": [
			"Pink",
			"Red",
			"Purple",
			"Blue"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How far away can a wolf smell its prey?",
		"options": [
			"Less than 100 meters",
			"Upto 500 meters",
			"Upto 1Km",
			"More than 2Km"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What do snakes use to smell?",
		"options": [
			"Skin",
			"Eyes",
			"Tongue",
			"Tail"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How many layers of skin does a chameleon have?",
		"options": [
			"One",
			"Two",
			"Three",
			"Four"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the largest type of frog?",
		"options": [
			"Goliath Frog",
			"Glass Frog",
			"Tomato Frog",
			"South American Horned Frog"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "How can you tell the age of most trees?",
		"options": [
			"Counting the leaves",
			"Height of the tree",
			"Depth of the tree root",
			"Counting the rings of the tree"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "How many eyes do caterpillars have?",
		"options": [
			"Four",
			"Eight",
			"Twelve",
			"Twenty"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the largest bird?",
		"options": [
			"Ostrich",
			"Vulture",
			"Eagle",
			"Albatross"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What color are elephant hawk-moths?",
		"options": [
			"Pink",
			"Purple",
			"Grey",
			"Black"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What are deciduous plant?",
		"options": [
			"Plant that keeps it's leaves always",
			"Plants that sheds its leaves every fall",
			"Plants that bear fruits",
			"Plants that do not bear fruits"
		],
		"answer": 1
	}
]